A Guide to the Records of Lieutenant Governor Timothy M. Kaine, 1995-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of Lieutenant Governor Timothy M. Kaine, 1995-2005
The Library of Virginia
42396
35.37 cubic feet (101 Boxes)
Virginia Lieutenant Governor
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Various items have been sealed for seventy-five years from the date of the document for privacy and/or security concerns.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Lieutenant Governor on 1 January 2006.
Biographical Information
Timothy M. Kaine was born on 26 February 1958 in St. Paul, Minnesota. He grew up in Kansas City and graduated from the University of Missouri-Columbia in 1979. While attending Harvard Law School, Kaine took a leave of absence to work with Jesuit missionaries as principal of the Institutio Tecnico Loyola, a Catholic vocational school in El Progreso, Honduras. Kaine graduated from Harvard Law School in 1983 and was admitted to the Virginia Bar. Practicing law in Richmond, Virginia, as director of the McCandlish Kaine law firm, Kaine specialized in housing discrimination cases. He received recognition from the Richmond Bar Association, the National Fair Housing Association, and Lawyers for Public Justice for his work with civil rights. In addition, Kaine taught legal ethics for six years at the University of Richmond Law School.
Kaine began his political career with an election to the Richmond City Council in 1994, serving as mayor from 1998 to 2001. During his four terms in the Richmond City Council, Kaine helped build new schools, encourage economic development, and implement the Project Exile Program to reduce violent crime. In 2001, Kaine was elected Lieutenant Governor under Governor Mark R. Warner. As Lieutenant Governor, Kaine supported state budget reform, education improvements, and the public broadcasting of the General Assembly. He served on the Governor's K-12 Accountability Workgroup, the Governor's Higher Education Summit, the Workforce Training Sub-Committee, the Secure Virginia Panel, the Citizens & Committees Sub-Committee, and chairman of the Disability Commission. In addition, Kaine worked on the Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee, the Virginia Military Advisory Council, and the Olmstead Task Force.
On 14 January 2006, Kaine was inaugurated as Governor of Virginia. He is married to Anne Bright Holton, youngest daughter of former Governor Linwood Holton. Anne and Tim have three children, Nat, Woody, and Annella.
Scope and Content
The Lieutenant Governor records consist of 101 archival boxes and are divided into three series. Series have been designated for Boards and Commissions, Constituent Correspondence, and Legislation Files & Supporting Documentation. These records document the work of Timothy M. Kaine as lieutenant governor under Governor Mark R Warner. The Boards & Commissions series contains useful documentation on some of the projects Kaine was involved in, especially the Secure Virginia Panel, Virginia's anti-terrorism task force. The bulk of the records can be found in the Constituent Correspondence series which includes letters sent to Lieutenant Governor Tim Kaine and Governor Mark Warner. Lastly, the Legislation Files and Supporting Documentation series provides valuable background information filed in the Office of the Lieutenant Governor.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Boards and Commissions, 1995-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)
Series II. Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2005
Series III. Legislative Files & Supporting Documentation, 1992-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)
Contents List
- Series I. Boards and Commissions, 1995-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)., Extent: 16 boxes. (Box 1-16)
  The Boards and Commissions series is housed in sixteen archival boxes and is arranged in six subseries. Subseries have been designated for Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee, Base Realignment & Closure, Disability Commission, Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, Olmstead Task Force, & Secure Virginia Panel. This series documents Tim Kaine's work on various boards & commissions as Lieutenant Governor.
  Arranged alphabetically by subseries.
  - Subseries A: Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee, 2004., 2 folders.
    The Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee subseries is housed in two archival folders. This subseries documents Tim Kaine's role as a member of the Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee. The Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee was appointed by the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors in response to a critical need to preserve existing affordable housing in Fairfax County. The subseries consists of notebook materials which were handed out at the 22 October 2004 meeting of the Affordable Housing Preservation Action Committee. Included is a list of members, charter, agenda, subcommittee assignments, housing facts, semiannual report, strategic plan, and other sundry items.
    - Notebook Materials
      - 2004 (Part 1) (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 2004 (Part 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Base Realignment & Closure (BRAC), 2004., 3 boxes.
    The Base Realignment and Closure subseries is housed in three archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries contains memorandums, minutes, correspondence, legislation, clippings, annual reports, and other sundry items. Significant within this subseries are files related to the Virginia Commission on Military Bases (VCOMB) which was created by Governor Mark R. Warner on 6 June 2003 by Executive Order 49 for the purpose of addressing the federal base realignment & closure for 2005. Additionally, there are files related to the Virginia Military Advisory Council which was reestablished in 2002 to identify & study and provide advice & comments to the Governor on issues of mutual concern to the Commonwealth and the Armed Forces of the United States.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Clippings
      - 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Encroachment, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fort Monroe, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - United States Joint Forces Command Briefing
      - 2003 (Part 1) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 2003 (Part 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commission on Military Bases
      - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Videotape, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Council
      - 2002 (Part 1) (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 2002 (Part 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C: Disability Commission, 1999-2005., 5 boxes.
    The Disability Commission subseries is housed in five archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order with chronological files arranged to the front. This subseries contains annual reports, publications, correspondence, agendas, memorandums, presentations, legislation, meeting summaries, clippings, press releases, and other sundry items. The subseries documents Tim Kaine's involvement on the Disability Commission which was formed in 1990 by House Joint Resolution 45 to identify legislative priorities for the General Assembly in order to provide ongoing support in developing & reviewing services & funding related to Virginians with disabilities. This subseries consists of chronological files between 1999 and 2005 which include miscellaneous information documenting meetings and other activities of the Disability Commission. In addition, there are various subject files related to such topics as autism, the Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, Medicaid, and the Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program.
    - 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 2-1-1 Virginia, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Alzheimer's Disease & Related Disorders Commission, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Autism, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Braille, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Children's Mental Health, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Delivering the Promise: Preliminary Report of Federal Agencies' Actions to Remove Barriers and Promote Community Integration, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Department of Rehabilitative Services, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Disability Services, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Elderly, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Endependence Center Incorporated, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - General, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - House Joint Resolutions, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Housing, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Housing Accessibility, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Housing Choice Vouchers, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Housing Consultant Report
      - 2003 (Part 1) (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - 2003 (Part 2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Housing Work Group
      - General, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Meetings, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Action Plan, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Letters, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Long Term Care, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Mary's Family, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Medicaid Buy-In
      - General, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - SunTrust, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Medicaid Updates & Briefings, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Medical Board of California v. Michael J. Hason, et al., 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Meetings
      - 2002 (Part 1) (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - 2002 (Part 2) (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - 2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - 2005 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - NCBDC & TAC Proposed Work Plan, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - New Medicaid Waiver, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Northern Neck Planning District Commission, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Publications, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Qualified Allocation Plan (QAP), 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Rehabilitation
      - 2002 (Part 1) (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 2002 (Part 2) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - RoadMap to Services, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Robert E. Rose Memorial Foundation, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - SHARE Homeless Intervention Program, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Social Security Act, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Specialized Transportation Council, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Statistical Record of the Virginia Medicaid Program and Other Indigent Health Care Programs, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Summary of Services, Programs, and Initiatives Provided to Virginians with Disabilities, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Transition Advocacy Team, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program
      - 2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Department for the Deaf & Hard of Hearing, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Office for Protection & Advocacy, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Waivers, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 2002-2005., 5 boxes.
    The Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation subseries is housed in four archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries contains memorandums, financial statements, marketing reports, mailers, annual reports, correspondence, agendas, minutes, press releases, publications, and other sundry items. This subseries documents the role of Timothy M. Kaine as a member of the Board of Trustees of the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation. Included is information on various board meetings between 2002 and 2005. In addition, there is a copy of "The Jamestown Project: Draft Development Concept Plan/Environmental Impact Statement" submitted by the National Park Service. The Jamestown Project consists of three volumes which analyze four action alternative plans for improvements at the Jamestown unit of the Colonial National Historic Park and the Jamestown unit of the Colonial National Historic Park and the Jamestown National Historic Site owned and managed by the Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities.
    - 2002 Feb.-June (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 2002 July-Aug. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 2002 Sept.-2003 April (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 2003 Nov.-2004 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 2004 Dec.-2005 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Background Materials for General Motors Appointment, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Board of Trustees Fall Meeting
      - 2002 Nov. 7-8 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - 2003 Nov. 17-18 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - 2004 Nov. 15-16
        - Part 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - 2005 Nov. 21-22
        - Part 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Part 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Board of Trustees Fall Meeting
      - 2002 May 23-24 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - 2003 May 15-16
        - Part 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - Part 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Board of Trustees & Board of Directors Joint Spring Meeting
      - 2004 May 13-14 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - 2005 May 19-20
        - Part 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - The Jamestown Project: Draft Development Concept Plan/Environmental Impact Statement
      - Vol. 1
        - Pages 1-94 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - Pages 95-215 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Vol. 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Vol. 3
        - Appendix A-G (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - Appendix H-L (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Subseries E: Olmstead Task Force, 2002-2003., 1 box.
    The Olmstead Task Force subseries is housed in one archival box and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries contains memorandums, reports, correspondence, agendas, notes, presentations, and other sundry items. The subseries documents the work of the task force established to develop an Olmstead plan for Virginia to serve persons with disabilities. The Olmstead Decision by the Supreme Court in 1999 upheld the U.S. Dept. of Justice's regulations mandating that states must administer their programs in the most integrated setting appropriate to the needs of persons with disabilities. The decision of Olmstead v. L.C. prohibits states from placing persons with disabilities in inappropriate institutional placements, asserting that, under the ADA, continued unjustified institutionalization is a violation of an individual's right to live in the most integrated setting appropriate to his/her needs and to have choices. This subseries includes information regarding the Olmstead v. L.C. Case, waiver meetings, and task force meetings. Also noteworthy is a copy of "One Community: Final Report of the Task Force to Develop an Olmstead Plan for Virginia."
    - Background, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Olmstead v. L.C., 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - One Community: Draft Final Report of the Task Force to Develop an Olmstead Plan for Virginia, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - One Community: Final Report of the Task Force to Develop an Olmstead Plan for Virginia, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Resource Utilization Groups (RUGs), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Task Force Meetings, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Team Meetings, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Waiver Meetings, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Subseries E: Secure Virginia Panel, 1999-2005., 2 boxes.
    The Secure Virginia Panel subseries is housed in two archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries contains agendas, minutes, correspondence, publications, reports, press releases, presentations, notes, and other sundry items. This subseries documents the work of the Lieutenant Governor as a member of the Secure Virginia Panel. The Secure Virginia Panel was established by Governor Mark R. Warner's Executive Order 7 directing state agencies to prepare or update emergency response plans, and designating points of contact with the administration for federal cooperation on homeland security issues. Noteworthy in this subseries are files related to the various sub panels of the Secure Virginia Panel including the Agribusiness Sub Panel, Citizen & Communities Sub Panel, First Responder Sub Panel, Government Operations & Funding Sub Panel, Health & Medical Sub Panel, Industry & Commerce Sub Panel, Technology Sub Panel, Transportation Sub Panel, and Utilities Sub Panel.
    - 2004
      - Part 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Part 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Citizen Corps, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Community Outreach & Awareness, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Preparedness Guides, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Press, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Resources, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Secure Virginia Initiative Panel, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sub Panels, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Terrorism Consequence Management, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Terrorism & Security Awareness Orientation Instructor Guide, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Terrorist Threat Assessment for the Secure Virginia Panel, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Series II: Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2005., Extent: 53 boxes. (Box 17-72)
  The Constituent Correspondence series is housed in fifty-three archival boxes and is arranged in two subseries. Subseries have been designated for Chronological Files & Subject Files. This series documents incoming correspondence received by the Office of the Lieutenant Governor between 2002 and 2005. In addition to correspondence, this series includes subject files which served as supporting documentation sent & received by the office to and from the Governor and Governor's Office Staff, Cabinet Secretaries and officials, legislators, State agencies, and the general public.
  - Subseries A: Chronological Files, 2002-2005., 26 boxes.
    This subseries is housed in twenty-six archival boxes and is arranged in chronological order. The subseries contains correspondence from constituents to Lieutenant Governor Tim Kaine & Governor Mark R. Warner between 2002 and 2004. Most of the correspondence includes a copy of Kaine's letter in response. The correspondence mainly relates to legal issues, college & employment recommendations, Eagle Scouts, teachers of the year, budget deficit & cuts, birthday greetings, requests for photos & biographies, bilingual ballots, historic tax credit program, legislation, invitations, salary increase for state employees, H.J. Resolution 56, health care costs, Federal Marriage Amendment, I-81 expansion, mental illness, personal appearances, Primary Interstate Waste Bill, car tax, immigration, partial-birth abortion, same-sex marriage, Hurricane Katrina, Senate Bill 873, and other topics. In addition, there is correspondence from inmates which is filed at the end of each year. Prominent correspondents consist of members of Warner's cabinet including Anita A. Rimler, Secretary of the Commonwealth, John Marshall, Secretary of Public Welfare, & Jane H. Woods, Secretary of Health & Human Services. The subseries also contains incoming & outgoing correspondence from Jeff Geiger, Director of Constituent Services, & Jeff Kraus, Administrative Aid.
    Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by correspondent.
    - 2002
      - A (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Ba-Be (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Bi-Bo (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Br-Bu (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Ca (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Ce-Co (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Cr-Cy (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Da-Di (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Do-Du (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Do-Du (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - E (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - F (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Ga-Gi (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Gl-Gu (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Ha-He (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Hi-Hu (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - J (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - K (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - La-Le (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Li-Ly (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Ma (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Mc (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Me-Mi (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Mo-Mu (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - N (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - O (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Pa-Pi (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Pl-Py (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Q (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Ro-Ry (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Sa-Se (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Sh-Sp (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - St-Sw (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - T (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Wa-We (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Webster, Elizabeth M. (videotape) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - We-Wh (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Wi-Wy (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Y-Z (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Do Not Respond Letters
        - General (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - C.C. (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Out of State (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Inmates
        - B-G (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - H-P (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - R (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - S-Y (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 2003
      - A (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Ba-Be (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Bi-Bo (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Br-By (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Ca-Ch (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Cl-Co (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Cr-Cu (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Da-De (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Di-Dw (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - E (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Fa-Fo (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Fr-Fu (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Ga-Go (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Gr-Gu (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Ha (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Harlow, Larry
        - Jan.-June (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - July-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - He-Ho (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Hu (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - I (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - J (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - K (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - La-Le (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Li-Ly (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Mac-Man (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Mar-May (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Mc-Mg (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Mi-Mo (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Mu-My (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - N (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - O (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Pa-Pi (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Pl-Pu (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Q (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Ro-Ry (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Sa-Sc (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Se-Si (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sk-Sta (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Ste-Sw (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Ta-Thompson (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Thorn-To (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Tr-Ty (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - U-V (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Wa-We (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Wh-Wi (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Wo-Woolwine (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Woolwine-Wr (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Y-Z (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Do Not Respond Letters
        - A-G (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - H-Mi (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Mu-W (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - White, Eileen (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - Out of State (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Inmates
        - A-H (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - J-P (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - R-W (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Sexual Orientation Non-Discrimination Letters (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 2004
      - A (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Ba-Bl (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Bo-Br (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Bu-By (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Ca-Cl (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Cob-Con (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Coo-Cy (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - D (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - E (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - F (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - G (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Ha (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - He-Hu (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - J (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - K (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - La-Lea (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Led-Lu (Box 34, Folder 5)